I'll now call to order the regular scheduled meeting of the Miami City Council.
Number two, public input and unscheduled personal appearances.
We have none.
Number three, A claims.
Motion.
Second.
All right.
Joe.
Hi.
Three B minutes from the February 3rd, 2026 regular meeting.
Motion.
Second.
3C ordered 2026 dash 06 for the rezoning of certain properties located at 1700B northwest.
This is the Jones.
Well, this is the next one.
1700.
They're not in the package.
They can sit in the opposite of the phone.
OK.
So, kind of show.
I hear.
So, see, starting with 1700B northwest, paraged investments.
They've, if you see in around town, there's some dumpster trailers that say,
we buy ugly houses.
And I will give them that.
They do do that.
But he definitely puts time and effort into it and what needs to go into these properties.
He's recently purchased a 1700B northwest.
This already has two properties on it.
It's a main residence and they, like a garage, like a mother-in-law sweep.
He's wanted to make it two properties.
So, they'll have two different addresses, two different meters, water meters.
So, we've got his own residential single family.
So, we'll have to present rezoning at multi-family.
And due to it already having existing residences on there and take it at most a lot,
we are going to ask to rezoning that to RM1 residential multi-family.
I don't see there's going to be any issues.
So, we're going to have two separate meters for each of the utilities.
We've got a garage to the apartment, too.
Yeah, sorry.
Yeah, a lot.
That was a white mountain.
You guys see where you were looking at.
Yeah.
Yeah, so it's the one with the the house and then the garage
So it's going right now like probably when they built that
He was probably like said it concluded the main property
Well, he's wanted to put two different residences in there
So we don't so we
So we've got to reason it multi-family if it's going to have two separate if you're not
Basically related to the primary residence
So
Well, I said we'll have separate meters selected new separate meters on that is electrical water
Does it already have those separate meters are they tied in to
existing
Yeah, okay, yeah
Yeah
Yeah, it's a single family just because the apartment went with the house when they built it
Sure, that's how
Not saying that's they people have ever rented it out to other people. I'm sure they have all but
Well, yeah, so now it's going to be legal because it'll be multi-family
3d orders 26 dash 07 206 dash 07 for the rezoning a certain property located at
H23 H to request case of this one was on our demo list
We had property hearings last summer
This was on schedule be demoed
Zack actually bought the house and get them out of the house himself
Which took the burden off of the city and he's wanting to
Build a tried-plex on the property of course it's for zone residues or single family because it was single family home
We have to do
Rm 2
It's going to be I don't know if you guys drove by it, but it
It burned probably two years ago, maybe
We finally got on the demo list property on it and show up. They defaulted and it was on our list to be torn down
He has torn it down. It's the lot's really not cleaned up yet, but it's it's it's getting there
I think this is one of the ones that he definitely bought an ugly house because it was I mean I
Zack's great work with he's been going you know by a lot of properties around town doing right keep
ness in the loop so
That's makes our job easy
Okay, three E contract for the my my regional airport QT pod in
4,000 self-serving fuel internal
It's the info 1000 we couldn't go to for the M5,000
I
So this is the feeling station and on the self-serving fuel out of the airport
From what I understand the fuel master is about 10 years old maybe a little more when you say
It's become obsolete so either way we got to update the pod
pedestal
We've kind of gone back and forth about going back with fuel master or QT we learned about QT
Some other area airports have the QT they seem to think it's more user friendly
We've kind of quizzed some pilots as I come in it was a unanimous vote
To recommend the QT at the airport board meeting so I have Brian Loman here who is
One of the reasons I will say that we kind of lean towards this because he's local
He's out of bottles of bill
With fuel master, you know, you kind of get put on hold talk to people. I mean I can call Brian
Anytime he's been great to work with
As far as what it does
I'm really not privy on that that's why I have Brian here so if you guys if you guys have any questions on the installation process how long it'll take
I'm just excited to team because one we have it's been a thorn in our side for a couple of years now
Just like when those based how do we're credit card terminal
It's basically a small window
Computer screen
File comes up puts in their tell number runs a credit card
Cool thing about the tell number is it actually tracks those so
If they're in a lot of fuel problem or anything like that you can tie it back to who's bought fuel
It runs all your aviation credit cards and then like a piece of master card
Cool thing about being the web base so if there is a problem with the terminal the company is out
Call rod and runs it
They can tie and tell you what's wrong and then get parts out to get it fixed
I've been with fuel master for a long time. It is a like a phone based so it goes to like a dial mode
This will be Internet-based, so it's a lot more responsive, even for a control on it, like if you've even put a fuel load coming in, so it's just kind of just going to manage this locally with WTRAS.
That's at the airport.
Then what's the cost?
It is, so if you'll master, it is 22,124 for the QT.
If you'll master it came in about 4G and more.
And again, even if they were here, I think myself, the board, felt that customer service was the big thing being having somebody here, a face.
So, and he could be here at any time.
I mean, all we have to do is pick up the phone and call him and interview him.
He or somebody, yeah.
In the airport, we're just, yeah, sure.
They, they wrecked, they unanimously recommended that we go as QT.
They're going to need additional fees associated with it, current court fees, or?
It's $16 a month.
That's actually, for the unbranded credit card network that will be through full of $66.
And how that works is, we actually would get the credit cards every day.
And we would send you guys a credit memo.
I will say the fuel measure we have, again, it's been, it's, life is, is done with, because some pilots are having trouble.
So, it stops their fuel like a certain amount.
And they can't get any more without pulling out, running it again, going and starting out over.
So, it's, it's been a long time coming.
For what I understand, I'm super excited to get this out there.
I'll make lunch from the food.
Second.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
He said that.
Both fiber game of internet services and extreme cloud IQ services at the library.
I'm just a colleague.
Oh, this is new since last time I was here.
So, every year we have to re-up our agreement with e-rate, which pays for the internet that we get at the library.
Last year was our last year on a five year extension contract.
And so we had to go off for a bit again this year.
IT looked over all the bits with me, and there's a scoring sheet.
And we ended up renewing with bolts again this year.
And so this just renews that so that it's year by year with five year
optional extension.
And then extreme cloud IQ provides us with the tracking data so that we know how many people are using
the library services.
So I 2425.
We had 5600 people come in and use our computers and 3300 people use our Wi-Fi.
And then this year so far with at 3100 use our computers and 579 access our Wi-Fi.
And so e-rate pays for that.
But we have to sign the agreement with bolt in order to get the services since it's
our building and our facility that uses it.
And we get a copy of them voices every month, but we don't pay anything out.
E-rate pays for it directly.
It's $900 a month.
I'll always this contract.
One year.
Okay.
Any other questions?
Hi.
Thank you.
Welcome.
I'm 3G vote on the new logo for the emergency management department.
Locals aren't they planned?
Good evening.
Melinda is home ill, so you've got me.
The city of Miami emergency management has not had a logo except for the old civil
defense triangle that we used for years.
Our website, our Facebook site, has not.
I initiated it in 2011 and it has not changed since then.
I'd like to change it.
So Melinda and I sat down and I looked at FEMA.
I looked at.
McAllisters I've looked at a lot of others, Washington and counties.
And the best logo we come up with was this one that y'all can see.
It should be.
It's in it the packet.
Yes.
It is in the packet.
The only place that this logo would be used would be on the door mat.
Should we ever, hopefully someday get a new vehicle.
The site like a door mat or that's what I call them.
And then on our Facebook site.
I wore this shirt tonight because this is what would remain.
as any logo that we would put on any thing that we would wore.
It is the mime with the white river and in the emergency management
and that because this would be way too much to put on a shirt
or a jacket or anything.
You can talk to Gary Longan about that because he wants a coat
and he wants that on it so there we go.
I know people.
Anyway, basically the guy, the one that we first started with was this one
and it is not in the packet.
It's not in the packet.
You're not considering it.
This is the one I want you to consider.
Go down and say yes because the reason you all have to do that is because
part of Melinda's policy that she proved.
I think for logos or Facebook or something.
I'm not for sure.
She's working on rebranding a lot.
Hey, you look nice on a watermark too.
Probably will not use it on any documents.
I don't anticipate using it on any documents because it would take a lot of color.
It's like a watermark.
The state has like three stars and actually the OEMA has changed theirs.
And it is the for preparedness mitigation recovery in response.
And it is huge and it is extremely busy.
This one's a bit busy but we wanted to flag and the eagle.
And we still have the old civil defense little sign right down there.
That will never go away.
I'm not crazy about it.
Just because I don't look at that and think of emergency management.
And for me, I think if you're going to put on the side of the vehicle or something.
I need to set it like it needs to.
For those who maybe can't read it.
They need to be able to see it and say okay that's emergency management.
But that's just me.
And I can tell you on any vehicle what we have right now is we have the small.
My Emma and it has emergency management in red.
That will also be on the truck and it will have.
It will be in reflective.
Because most of your emergency management vehicles around the state city or county.
We'll have with exception of a few.
We'll have emergency management in red across the back.
They will also have the blue and the.
I think it's silver reflective tape.
We had that.
before we had a big eagle and just the city emblem.
I'm for it.
I make motion.
I'll second.
I never for it.
Other new businesses, if any, which is a
reason since the post of this agenda.
I have none.
We have five staff reports.
And there it looks like we have reports on the city manager.
Budget amendments and the convention and visitors,
bureau, tourism, and the questions on those.
Great job, Tender.
What are the big things excited to see that?
Number six, mayor and council committee announcements.
So our mayor today, he is down in San Antonio recruiting new business.
So we're all excited about that.
So let's hope that they come back a lot of good news.
Number seven, city manager communications.
Okay.
And number eight adjournment.
Second.
Good job, guys.
All right.